Guide to the Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records, 1893-2008.
Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records
- Series IV. Cornell University Theatre and Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Scripts and Prompt Books
    - A Match for the Devil by Norman Nicholson, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - The Female Woild by Kenneth James Konlande, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - In a Mirror Darkly by Eugene Feist, undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Mania, Mania, Who's Got the Mania by Preston, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Ancient Aztec Legend by Margaret Brobston, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - The Temptation of Saint Antonio by Stephen Radkoff, undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - The Man Who Woke Up by Anne Walters, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Red Two by James E. Michael, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - A Penny for Charon by Herman A. Miller, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - High Life by Janet K. Smith, undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - The Squirrel Cage by William H. Putch, undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Cinderella by Rossini adapted by Gil Gallagher, undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - A Moment of Quiet by Jean Ennui, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - The Shorn Lambs by John Mock, undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - The Golden Goose by Roberta Lanouette, undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - The Long Hill by Calista Barker Clark, undated (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Steps of Sand by Bert Pollock, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Song Without End by Louis C. Adelman, undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - End of a Season by Gloria Goldsmith (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Cicero by Upton Sinclair, 1960; (with letter) (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - A Different Drummer, undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - A Different Drummer by Gene McKinney, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Sharp Practices, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - The Man on the Bar Stool by Alex Panas; To Live in Faith by Esther M. Hawley; A King of a Man by Norton Cooper; The House with Hanging Feet by Gordon Reston; The Secret of the Drums by Priscilla Kiefer, circa 1953 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Everyman, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Judas, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - The House by the Stable by Charles Williams; Three Actors and Their Drama; The Little Man; Come on Kid, Let's Go to Sleep; The Doctor and the Devils, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Heermans Plays (And May God Have Mercy by Charles Mendick, 1936-1937 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Heermans Plays (Fair Day Thursday, and Private Performance by Patricia Anne Colbert; Oblivion Is Not Here by Margaret Taylor; Postwar Planning by Andreas Ibanov (James D. Breckenridge); Spoil by Walter Scheinman; Up Sword by Roy I. Friedlander, 1943-1946 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Heermans Plays (And the Pursuit of Happiness by William Marshall; Superman's Wife by Jacob Regal; Tomorrow Without Leave by Walter Scheinman; Mea Culpa by Walter Scheinman; Island by John Brook; Mine Eyes Have Seen by Gene Wyckoff), 1942-1946 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Heermans Plays (Melting Pot, and The Woman in Bed by Frederick M. Shelley III; American Pieta by Albert N. Perretta), 1942 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Heermans Plays (Gerda's Vision; Prince John; Insurrection in Heaven by Albert Perretta), 1943 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Heermans Plays (Private Performance by Patricia Anne Colbert; Retreat by Walter Scheinman; The Reprieve, and Five Characters in Search of Saroyan by Roy I. Friedlander), 1943-1946 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - The Dusk of Battle by Walter Scheinman; The Trojan Horse by Archibald MacLeigh; No Doubt About It by Brian Dillon, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Chicago by Gary Simpson, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Written in the Stars by Hugh Carstairs; Splendid Isloation by Everett Crum; Progression by Charles Lebrun; The Clock by Jerome Jerrold, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Traffic Signals by A. M. Drummond (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Traffic Signals Part II by A. M. Drummond, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - The Prize by Roderick Robertson; The Time Ran by Joanna Russ, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Paradiso! Paradiso! by Jan Wahl; The Muskrat Ramble by Stephen R. Franken; One Hundred Pounds by Judy Roberts; Come for Tea by Judith Shields, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Confessional by Don Biederman; Three Cheers for Woody by Monroe Scott; Soft Rains Will Come by Emily Frenkel; Fountain of Knowledge by Brian Dillon, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Champeen of the Canawl by E. Kamarck; Right You Are! (If You Think So) Acts I, II, III; The Absent-Minded Professor Has Breakfast by Sidney S. Kirschner, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - The Fall of the City, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Stranger in the House by William H. Putch, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Yankee Land by C. A. Logan, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      script and notes
    - Late for Dinner by Patricia Schewerman; Payday Night by Story Talbot; Marriage Wheel by Joel Climenhaga, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Steps of Sand; Across Big Mountain and Years of the Harvest by Bert Pollock, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Once Upon a Hill (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Once Upon a Hill individual scripts, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Once Upon a Hill individual music, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Once Upon a Hill production notes, 1950-1957 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Once Upon a Hill, undated (Box 29, Folder 26-27)
    - The Groove (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Tickless Time (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - The Wooden Leg (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - The Eternal Quadrangle (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Carnival (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Who Knows Best (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - The Sheaphardes' Play (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Beauty and the Jacobin (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Be It Ever So Humble by M.B. Hellinger (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - The Long Christmas Dinner (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - No Answer by Dan Tuttle, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Too Good is Unhealthy by Angela Marsden Messenger, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Pas de Deux by Daniel Brooke, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Climate of Fear by Charles Aycock Poe, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - He Chose to Dream by Theodore Allen, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Farmers' Holiday by Thomas Searles, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Trial by Fire by George H. Dunne, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - The Cloak by Arthur Lithgow, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - The Dream Weaver by Antonio Buero Vallejo, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Crazy Man by Donald F. Weinberger, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Page of Life by Robert Goodman, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - The Passionate Pilgrims by Douglas Watt, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - … the worker who … by Irwin J. Liebowitz, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Silver Slippers by Seymour A. Gross, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - The Radiator by Gabriel Levenson, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Violet J. Brown plays (By the Waters of Babylon; Where Angels Fear; Lucrezia; The Great American Play or America Sings!), 1934 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Reunion, and The Man Who Defied God by C. B. Moss, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Sattiday Night, and Fle Fro the Pres by G. H. Levenson, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - The Frogs Become America (with George Jean Nathan as a character), undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Charles J. Bruneel Plays (Informal Date; Reunion; Smart Girl; Together Alone, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - The Sons of Setewa by Herbert Yenne (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Wrong Number by Charles Brunelle; The Poet or Peter? by Homer E. Baker; Ars Gratia Artis by Lawrence Abbott or Seymour Gross and John Smith; Reunion by Charles Lebrun), undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - The Vicious Cycle by Ted Hatlen; The Impenetrable Night, and Fugue by Violet Joyce Brown; America's Melting Pot, and Careerdom or Wifedom, and A Fifty-Fifty Chance by Ruth Press, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Ars Gratia Artis by Seymour A. Gross; The Blind Goddess, and Town Girl by Annette R. Baker; Back on the Game by J. R. Hefler; A Playwright Looks at Life by Seymour B. Berkowitz; Thirteen Gardenias by Barbara P. Buchanan, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - 1945 Anvil Revue; The Restless Sea by Lacy Baldy (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - To Learn To Love by William I. Oliver; The Prickly Pear; From Rags to Riches by Charles A. Taylor, undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Don Juan Tenorio by Jose Zorrilla y Moral, translated by William I. Oliver, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Clive of India; Dr. Gailey's Lecture by Anthony G. Dower; Silver Slippers; A Babe in Time by Leonard Feinstein, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Helen of Troy by Joseph W. Miller script, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Over the Mountain and Proof by Robert Hethmon; From Bad to Better and Love Abetted by Lea Shampanier; The Weaker Souls by James R. Crane; Whistle + Stop, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Jimmy's Surprise by Lea Shampanier; Play #1 by Frank E. Fairchild, Jr.; Beyond the Law and the Damned by Eldridge; The Dead Yet Living by James P. Crane; The Oil That Heals and Sentimental Value by Anthony Geiss, undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Until the Coroner Comes by Anthony Geiss; No Heaven for Me, and The Gay People, and untitled by Nestor Ernest Kuzmin; Night Watch; Will to Live by Lea Shampanier; The Answer Man by William E. Johnson, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Shavelson plays - So This Is Love, and Portrait of Eternity by Melville Shavelson, undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Heermans plays (Heavy Traffic by C.B. Moss; Superman by John Brookes; The Better Angels by Burt Monroe; America Enters the War by Esther Marsh; Harness by Arnold Fraleigh; By the Rivers of Babylon by Violet J. Brown; Symphony by Ralph Tomfrelt; Man Hunt b, undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Heermans plays (The Sidewalk by Beatrice Marks; Dark Earth by Morris Frank; Town and Gown by Seymour B. Beckmitz; Self Evident Truths by Robert Gordman; The Quiet of Tomorrow by Ralph Cohn), undated (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Heermans plays (What Price the Melting Pot? By Beatrice Marks; The Melody of Discord; The Great American Play by Elvira M.J.H. Lester; Our Wiser Sons by S. A. Gross; It's a Wow by Ruth A. Beck)), undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Written in the Stars by Annete Baker; Orchids for Laurels by Seymour A. Gross; illegible by Hillman; untitled by Henry Hillman; Services Rendered by M.B. Hellinger; The People's Friend by Deane A. Dunloy, undated (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Jobie and The Simple Farming Man by Daniel N. Fader; Murdering by Alice Dennis Weschke; Stampede Bluff, undated (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Sabotage by Charles Hellem, William Valcros and Pol d'Estoc (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - A Good Woman by George Middleton (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - The Tents of the Arabs (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - The Choir Rehearsal (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Cheese Colossus (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Pullman Car Hiawatha (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - This Property is Condemned by Tennessee Williams (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - The Catalogue (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - The Feast of the Holy Innocents by S. Marshall Ilsley (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - The Aulis Difficulty (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Minnie Field (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - An Idea for Charlie and The Harvester by Wilmer Hayden Welsh; One Summer's Day by Ellen Lawson; Three Cheers for Woody by Munroe Scott; Touchdown for Shakespeare by Adolyn Arline, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Muskrat Ramble by Stephen R. Franken; The Devil Among the Skins; Transition: A Game by David Seidler; Waiting for Santy by S. J. Perelman; To Count Thirteen by Marion L. Miller; The Ivory Gate by Perry Mason, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union plays, 1935-1937 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - The Christmas Story, Old and New by Olla Rickett and Robert Rhodes, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - UNESCO plays (New Fountains by Lee Gilmore; To Live in Faith by Esther M. Hawley), 1953 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - New York State plays (A Day in the Vineyard by Irene Baker and A. M. Drummond; Family Co-operative by Ella L. Thurston; Let's Get on With the Marryin', and Raisin' th' Devil by Robert E. Gard), 1940 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - American Agriculturalist Prize Plays (Fractions by Floyd Spicer Armstrong; Who is Wellington? by Carrie W. Ladd; Nothing Doing by Grace Smith Beers; The Electric Fence by M.F. Partridge), 1940 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Reflection in the Dark by Emily Frenkel; To Dwell in the Sun by William I. Oliver, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Christmas plays (The Line by Morris Martin; Christmas Eve Story by Alastair Cooke; The Christmas Invasion), undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Il Teatro Alla Moda by Benedetto Marcello, translated by William Strunk, Jr., 1944 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - The Cellar by Michael Chayes; Without Return by O'Gene U. Heele; Then the Winning School-boy by John Falstaff; Bachelor of Unemployment by Theodore Allen; Clam Digger by John Brown, Jr., 1936 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Twilight Bar by Arthur Koestler, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - The Crime in Lansing by J. A. Withey, 1953; (about Edward H. Rulloff) (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - An Afternoon Fantasy by Charles Rodin, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Woodman, Chop That Tree by Division of Information, WPB, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Another Kate by Arthur Francis Brash, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Crown of Choice by M. C. Kuner, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Set It In Troy, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - How to Grow a Musical, (in Spanish) (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Fishin' Weather by Samuel Sidney Hale; Bugles at Noon; Moses, Saroyan and Welles, 1940, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Cry Witch by Marion L. Miller; Pillar of Salt by Wilmer Hayden Welsh; Second Degree by Ian Elliot; Pierrot-in-the-Round by Donald Streibig; Three Cheers for Woody by Munroe Scott; A Heavy Sound Breaks In by Richard Farina; Waiting for Santy by S. J. Perelman (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Behind the Beyond by Stephen Leacock; Ka La'Ni by Dorothy Stewart; Polski, and Hell and High Water by William D. Hammack; Three Cheers for Woody by Monroe Scott; Waiting for Santy by S. J. Perelman; The Romantic Family by Q. Vermout (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Behind the Beyond (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - General Store (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - As Good As She Is Beautiful (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Plots and Playwrights (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - The Trysting Place (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Beautiful Despot (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Scientific Love by Russell Craft '23, undated (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Une Aimable Lingère by Tristan Bernard; The Man Who Went Riding by James B. Gitlitz; A Bow Makes the Knot by Hal Lehrman; The Hiding of Black Bill by M. T. Herrick; The Stradivarius by Max Maurey, undated (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - The Boulingrins by Georges Courteline translated by L.B. Crabtree; The Chosen, Grandma Columbine, and The Miracle by DeElbert Keenan, undated (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Betsy Anne by Felicity Gray, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Plays from contest: Up in the Air; The New Act by Sima Kaya; A Girl, the Letters and a Spy by The Marionette; Shattered Hopes by Cytherea Jones; The Moles by Peter Parr; A Woman of Advanced Ideas by A.B.C. (William J. Rapp); From Four Till Five, In the Shadow, and The Gift of Gab by Bertram F. Willcox; The Old Order Changeth, circa 1916 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Playwriting Contest evaluations, 1916-1917 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Parrotage by L.W. (Louise Wilkeson) O'Connell; The Pasha by William Jourdan Rapp; Gregg by William Jourdan Rapp and Walter Marquis, 1922, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Kitchen Company by G. L. Freeman; Stranger by Paul Duval; The Culmination by Saul Bernstein; The Country Ain't so Dumb After All by A.S.W. DeKalb; The Game of Life by E.G. Hatch; An Orchid by R.L. Craft; Untitled by Marjory Campbell McMullen; Cross-Purposes by Julia Eaton, undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - The Mother of Barbara; The Slippers That Broke of Themselves by Marie Drennan; Malchus by Arthur F. Nall; Fish for Dinner; Fire From Heaven; The Initiation by Arthur M. Coon; Signor Toto by Aristide D'Angelo, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - The Muff Diver by George Fass; Battling Byron, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - You were nice when you were young by Jean Anouilh (translated by James Clancy), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Chorale by Eva Wolas; What So Proudly We Hailed and Bowl of Cherries by Melville Shavelson; Good Evening, Mr. Senator by J.A. Clausen; O, Say Can You See by Arthur M. Levine; Come To Judgement, Jail Bait and Mother of Fame by Charles Joelson; Love is an Attitude, One Star Still Shines and Cut is the Thread by Leonard Feinstein, 1935-1936 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - The Power of the Press by Homer E. Baker; Let There Be Light and Lights Out! by Charles Brunelle; Forfeit, Clam Digger, The War and Jones (1936), The War and Jones (1935) and The Life of John Doe by S.B. Berkowitz; Cabbages and Kings by Benjamin F. Farber, Jr., 1935-1936 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - A Dirty Trick, Fool's Luck and His Last Crime by John Brand; You Know, or You Don't Know by Virginia Campbell, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - The Lake Guns of Seneca and Cayuga by A.M. Drummond, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - More Upstate New York Plays. Edited by A.M. Drummond and E.L. Kamarck. Project for New York State Plays., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - So This is College by Bertha J. Kotwica (Heermans Playwriting Contest) (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Her Heart was Richer Than Gold by Martin Sampson (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Sophocles' King Oedipus - Author: Sophocles - Director: M. Carlson, 1963; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Under the Gaslight - Author: Daly - Director: M. Carlson, August 1963; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - The Great God Brown - Author: O'Neill - Director: M. Carlson, 1962; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - The Lady's Not for Burning - Author: Frye - Director: M. Carlson, July 1963; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Galileo - Author: Brecht - Director: M. Carlson, July 1963; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Volpone - Author: Moliere - Director: M. Carlson, May 1961; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
    - The Bald Soprano - Author: Ionesco - Director: M. Carlson, 1966; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Journey of the Fifth Horse - Author: Ribman - Director: J. Clancy, March 1969; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Home - Author: Storey - Director: P. Stelzer, August 1972; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - A Month in the Country - Author: Turgenev - Director: M. Carlson, October 1977; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - The Empire Builders - Author: Vian - Director: P. Stelzer, October 1972; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Richard III - Author: Shakespeare - Director: M. Carlson, 1966; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - The Physicists - Author: Durrenmatt - Director: M. Carlson, December 1965; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - The Willow Copse - Author: Boucicault - Director: M. Carlson, August 1964; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - The Difficult Hour III - Author: P. Lagerkvist - Director: M. Carlson, 1966; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - The Story of Vasco - Author: Schehade, 1963; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - The School for Wives - Author: Moliere - Director: J. Clancy, June 1952; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Lady Windermere's Fan - Author: Wilde - Director: J. Clancy, Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - As You Like It - Author: Shakespeare - Director: J. Clancy, March 1968; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - An Evening of French Theatre and Music - Stage Director: J. Clancy [included works: "Mr. Me," "Useless Civility," "Conversation-Symphonette" and "The Sonata or How to Speak Music" by Jean Tardieu; "Enfantillages Pittoresques" and "Sports et Divertissements" by Erik Satie; "The Deceased" by Rene de Obaldia; "La Voix Humaine" by Francis Poulenc cna Jean Cocteau, October 1975; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Beaux Strategem - Author: Farquhar - Director: J. Clancy, July 1964; Prompt book (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - School for Scandal - Author: Sheridan - Director: J. Clancy, August 1971; Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - The Haunted House - Author: Plautus - Director: R. Smyth, Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - The Changeling - Author: Rowley - Director: J. Clancy, December 1969; Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Acharnians - Author: Aristophanes - Director: J. Clancy, November 1968; Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Papa is All - Author: Greene - Director: H. Lee Adey, May 1957; Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Lower Depths - Author: Gorky - Director: J. Clancy, April 1976; Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Taming of the Shrew - Author: Shakespeare - Director: J. Clancy, July 1972; Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Country Wife - Author: Wycherly, October 1953; Prompt book (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - The Cardiff Giant, Prompt book and scripts (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
    - Strife - Author: J. Galsworthy, Prompt book and scripts (Box 33, Folder 11-12)
    - Everyman (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Raisin' the Devil - Author: R. Gard (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Heermans Prize plays: Farmers' Holiday by Boris Bittker; The Good Samaritan by William Kuchmy (1937); You All Want Something and The Young Go First by Arthur M. Levine; Basement Flat by Edward Kamarck (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Mary Stuart - Author: Schiller - Director: J. Clancy, February 1968; Prompt book (Box 38)
    - One-act plays for A. M. Drummond course, 1933-1938
      - "A Piece of Pie" (1938), "Perspective," "A Piece of Pie" (1937) and "A Statement to the Press" by Alan F. Mock; "A One-Act Play" and "Love is Blind" by Sander A. Yellin (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Play notes (by A.M. Drummond); "As Good As She Was Beautiful" by J.W. Miller; "Humble Servant" by Clare Foot; "Vigil" by Alexander Zeeve(?); "The Practised Hand" by Harold E. Johnson (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - "Chatterton's Child" and "The Organ" by Martin Squires; "Another Midsummer Night" and "Three Sought for Death" by Howard Rogers Houston (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - "Life is Real-The Rose is Red," "The Great American Tragedy" and "Hercul Zaba" by Peter Kuchmy (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - "For the Good of the House," "The Better Part of Valor" (original and revised), "Neverland" and "The Death of the Hired Man" by Eugene Simonoff; "The Broken Chain," "The Widow," "There's a Bee-yo-tiful Moon!" and "Blessed Be Those Who Believe" by M.L. Munn (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - "The Bachelor Benedict," "The Country of the Blind" and "Bivouac" by A.C. Hartnett; "If It's a Goldfinch Picture...," "The Way Out" and "Till Death Us Do Part" by Marvin Fenster (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - "And God Rested" and "Bachaanal" by Arthur F. Neumann; "Uncle Benny Said So," "We Let It Happen," "Cordial's Ready," "The Spur of the Moment" and "To Soothe the Sting" by Mildred Harriet Teitelman (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - "Black Isn't Only a Color," "As Maine Goes," "Saturday" (Acts I-III) by Jacques Anson Finke; "Some Women Never Do" (original and rewrite), "A Slice of Sea Life" by F. Ford (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - "Outpost" and "Expelled" (original and rewrite) by George Engles, Jr.; "Oath to Hippocrates," "The Styx Runs Dry," "Rails, Preferred," "Thy Kingdom Come" and "Oh Mighty Pen!" by Martin F. Beck (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - "Eternity in their Heart," "Sufficient Lubrication," "At Any Cost" and "Among the Living" by Jane B. Mann; "A Broken Reed" (original and rewrite) and "In The Night" by Milton Gilberg (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - "Heart on her Sleeve," "I Have a Secret" and The New Yorker No. 1" by Bettina Azzarito (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - "He Knew What He Wanted," "Fated Love," "Men and Women," "The Future of the Thing" and "Ave Imperator" by Joseph W. Miller (Box 32, Folder 20)